你想我么 伽尔
Did you miss me, Gal?
玛达莲娜 我可是不远万里来看你呢
Madalena, I have traveled 1,000 miles to see you.
我和强盗们战斗
I fought pirates.
数十次差点儿丢了命
I stared death in the face a dozen times,
而我克服千难万阻 就为了去找一个女人
and I did all that to be with a woman
那个女人抛弃了我无条件的爱 选择了一个凶暴残忍的男人
who chose a fierce and cruel man over my unconditional love.
-所以 -我是想你了 是的
- So... - You crossed my mind, yes.
那你见了我肿么不高兴
Then why didn't you act happy to see me?
老实说 我不知道什么该有感觉
To be honest, I don't know how to feel.
伊莎贝拉告诉我 是你想我救你
Isabella told me you wanted me to rescue you.
你知道我要来了吗
Did you even know I was coming?
嗯 我今天早些时候知道的 我一听到这消息
Well, I found out earlier today, and as soon as I did,
我就想了一个我们在一起的计划
I made a plan for us to be together.
嗯 好吧 我也有个计划
Yeah, well, I had a plan, as well.
我们住在一个海边小屋里
We were gonna live in a cottage by the sea.
在那儿啪啪啪 种植一片庄园
We were gonna make love, plant a garden...
生儿育女
Have children.
我歌唱你的美丽
I was gonna sing songs of your beauty.
啊 伽尔
Oh, Gal.
那听起来可真可怕
That sounds awful.
看看四周吧
Look around.
我住在一个城堡里
I live in a castle.
你知道我对我自己有了什么认识吗
And you know what I've learned about myself?
我真的是追求物质的人
I really like stuff.
我是说 我为什么要放弃这一切
I mean, why would I give all this up
去当一个肥胖的怀孕农妇呢
to get fat and pregnant and grow my own food?
所以 你并不想让我来
So, you didn't want me to come?
我不该相信伊莎贝拉的
I should never have trusted Isabella.
这么娇小的人怎么撒这种弥天大谎呢
How could someone so small tell such a big lie?
好了 这些都不重要了
Well, none of that matters now.
我有一个计划 能够让我留下来当王后
I have a plan that will allow me to remain as queen,
而你会是受我照顾的
and you will be well taken care of as my...
特殊伙伴
Special companion.
你是想说当你的小白脸吧
Your boy toy, you mean.
你就是这样看待我的吗 是吧
Is that how you see me? Hmm?
那个衣着干净入时 长相粗犷英俊
As some well-groomed, ruggedly handsome,
性格却又特别敏感的玩物
yet oddly delicate-featured plaything?
是的
Yeah.
玛达莲娜 我得告诉你
Madalena, I've got something to say,
而且我真的是跋涉了千山万水来告诉你
and I've come a really, really long way to say it.
噢 不
Oh, no.
#我想要你 我需要你#
# I want you, I need you #
#你刺痛我心 我为你洒热血#
# You cut me, and I bleed you #
#你是首优美的诗#
# You're like some kind of sonnet #
#我只想读你读到痴#
# All I want to do is read you #
-#我爱你# - 我知道
- # And I love you # - I know.
-#我是说我爱你# - 是的 谢谢
- # I mean I love you # - Yes. Thanks.
-#我都说我爱你了# - 你确实爱我
- # I said I love you # - You did.
#为何你不有所回应#
# And now don't you want to tell me something, too? #
#我爱你#
# I love you #
#就像我爱任何人一样爱你#
# As much as someone like me can love anyone #
嗯
Huh?
#我是说 我爱别人关切我们的凝视眼神#
# I mean, I love how we make people stare #
#就像我们是登峰造极的一对#
# We're quite the stunning pair #
#换句话说 你爱我#
# In other words, you love me #
#就像我爱任何人一样爱你#
# As much as someone like me can love anyone #
好吧
Okay.
#我是说 我爱我们的床笫之欢#
# I mean, I love how when we hit the hay #
#那仿若人间天堂#
# It's more than just okay #
是吗
Right?
#我只能说是一般般而已#
# I'd absolutely say more like middling to fair #
嗯 等等 什么
Yeah. Wait. What?
#与我共舞吧#
# Dance with me #
#你看不出我们多么光彩夺目吗#
# Can't you see how freaking gorgeous we look? #
#你感受不到我们疯狂的心跳吗#
# Can't you feel the frantic beat of our hearts #
#我们身体每个部位都在摩擦摩擦 似魔鬼的步伐#
# As our various parts rub with such delicious friction? #
#那么 这就是你真正...#
# So, that's all you really... #
#与我共舞吧#
# Dance with me #
#已然开始 为何停止#
# Why not finish what's already begun? #
#那么 你所言之事便是真的爱我#
# So, what you're saying is you love me #
-#我爱你# -#真的爱我#
- # I love you # - # Really love me #
-#我爱你# -#永远爱我#
- # I love you # - # And always loved me? #
#就像我爱任何人一样爱你#
# As much as someone like me can love anyone #
你现在清楚了吧
Does that clear things up for you?
不
No.
你什么时候学的跳舞
And when did you learn how to dance?
你听见了么 加雷斯
Are you hearing this, Gareth?
我自己的老婆想骗我杀了我最喜欢的厨子
My own wife tries to trick me into killing my favorite chef
以拯救她的前男友
so she can save her ex-boyfriend.
你确定是她干的
You sure it was her?
美若天仙 纤纤细腰 大大的眼
Pretty girl, tiny waist, big eyes?
必须的 陛下
Definitely, My King.
没人比我更难过了 加雷斯
No one has it as bad as I do, Gareth.
- 没人 - 啊啊啊啊啊啊
- No one! - Aaaaaaaah!
嗯 别担心
Uh... Don't worry.
为什么我总要忍受别人这样对待我
Why do I continually allow people to treat me this way?
噢 拜托了
Oh, come on.
忘了我是个国王 给我点朋友的意见吧
Forget I'm your king and talk to me like your friend.
好的
All right.
你表现得像只猪一样
You keep acting like a prat.
你应该更老练一点的
You need to be more of a geezer.
你知道的 我已经劝了你一次又一次
You know, I've tried to tell you time and time again.
可你全当耳旁风了
You don't turn your ear.
啊 加雷斯
Oh, Gareth.
我一个字也听不懂哇
I can't understand a word you say.
那我问问你
Let me ask you this, then.
你喜欢我吗 加雷斯
Do you like me, Gareth?
- 我是说 你懂的 就 作为一个平常人 - 啊啊啊啊啊
- I mean, you know, as a... as a person? - Aaaaaaah!
我得走了
I got to go.
我的王后叫我呢
My queen needs me.
-你的王后 -嗯
- Your queen? - Mm.
你们都听见了么 现在是他的王后了
Are you hearing this? Now it's his queen.
好的 去吧
Fine. Go ahead.
你也走吧 这个狠心的负心汉
Leave me, too. Be that guy.
滚 滚
Go. Go.
嗯 好的
Yeah, okay.
我为什么酱紫
Why am I like this?
为什么我总是一次次被人辜负
Why do I continually allow people to treat me this way?
-陛下 -嗯
- Sire! - Hmm?
我 我想我有办法帮你
I-I think I know something that may help you.
真的吗 说
Really? What?
你听说过赞安诺么
Have you ever heard of Xanax?
赞安诺
Xanax?
是那个听说了很遍新魔法师吗
Is he that new magician I'm hearing so much about?
梅林的继承者
Merlin's replacement?
是的 陛下
Yes, My King.
我 我偶尔从他那儿买草药
I-I occasionally buy herbs from him.
草药 为什么 为了做饭
Herbs? For what? F-f-for cooking?
嗯 为 为了做饭
Yeah... f-for cooking.
好的 可以试试咯 我们去见见赞安诺吧
All right, it's worth a shot. Let's go see Xanax.
我应该穿的更休闲风的
I should probably put on something more casual.
褐色那件啦
The brown.
啊 嗨
Uh, hi.
嗯 为什么我们回到地牢呢
Um, why are we back in the dungeon?
就在这儿等着 到时候我会来接你的
Just wait here. I'll come get you when it's time.
有人正在赶来 帮忙实现我的计划
Someone's coming to help execute my plan.
快走
Move along.
伽尔凡特 伽尔凡特
Galavant! Galavant!
我以为你已经死了
I thought you were dead.
你是说因为你背叛了我 他们会把我吊死
You mean because you betrayed me, you thought they would hang me?
就因为你的背叛
Because you betrayed me?
噢 相信我 先生
Oh, trust me, sir,
我他妈就是因为她才会进这儿的
I have been guilting the crap out of her down here.
理查德国王说如果我不能把珠宝和你送来
King Richard said if I didn't deliver the jewel and you,
他就会杀了我的父母
he would kill my parents.
我试过警告你
I tried to warn you...
那么多歌曲 那么多私语
so many songs, so many asides.
重点是 玛达莲娜王后
The point is, Queen Madalena,
你已经得到了珠宝 你也得到了伽尔凡特
you have the jewel and you have Galavant.
-你必须放了我的父母了 -是么
- You must release my parents. - Must I?
-是的 你不得不放 -是么
- Yes. You have to. - Have I?
-是的 -真的么
- Yes. - Really?
你为什么重复反问我说的每句话
Why are you just repeating everything I say as a question?
我是重复反问你说的每句话吗
Am I just repeating everything you say as a question?
你 听不见么
You... Don't hear it?
-我听见了 是的 - 是呀
-I hear it. Yeah. - Yeah.
-你的确是有在重复
- You're sort of doing it a little bit.
我和理查德国王有个交易
- I had a deal with King Richard.
我亲爱的姑娘
My dear girl...
我虽不是理查德国王
I am not King Richard.
但我就喜欢杀
But I will enjoy killing the
吃我残羹冷炙的女孩
girl who tried to eat my leftover man mutton.
有木有热觉得很不舒服
Is... Anyone else uncomfortable?
加雷斯
Gareth.
割下她的脸
Cut her face.
折磨剩余的人
Torture the rest.
-伽尔 -什么
- Gala... - Excuse me?
我说折磨他们 有问题吗
I said torture them. Is there a problem?
不 一点儿问题也没有
No. There's not a problem.
我喜欢折磨人 我很擅长咧
I like torturing. I'm pretty good at it.
我曾经让一个只剩一个头和一根手指的
I once kept a guy alive for a week,
家伙活了一个礼拜呢
and he was just a head and a finger.
但那是国王下的令
But that order came from the king,
我为国王效劳
and I serve My King.
你的国王很虚弱 加雷斯 你知道的
Your king is weak, Gareth. You know this.
他哭得像个婴儿 心软得像个娘们
He cries like a baby, he cares like a woman.
他还喜欢制作剪纸小板凳呢
He makes decoupage footstools as a hobby.
嗨 那是我的生日礼物
Hey! That was a birthday present.
他送给我的 让我好让我能坐下
He got me that so I could have a sit down.
你就是一条狗 加雷斯
You're a dog, Gareth.
狗需要一个强大的主人
And a dog needs a strong master.
干掉他们
Now sic'em.
我们到了 先生
Here we are, sir.
我们安全吗
Are we safe?
这里的人看起来有那么一丢丢狡猾
This neighborhood looks a little dodgy.
别担心 陛下 我们没事哒
Don't worry, sire, we'll be fine.
只要 试着不要害怕
Just... Try not to look scared.
你好啊 见到你很高兴
Hello. Nice to see you.
你们要干啥
What do you want?
嗯 我们到这来找赞安诺
Uh, we're here to see Xanax.
他在阁楼上
He's in the attic.
妈妈 那是实验室
Mom! It's a laboratory!
你叫它实验室嘛
Call it a laboratory.
它就是个阁楼
It's an attic.
呼 真的超温馨哒
Hmm. This is... Cozy.
理查德国王 请允许我介绍魔法师赞安诺
King Richard, may I present Xanax The Magician.
实际上 我这魔法师的称呼
Actually, I'm not legally allowed
还没得到业界许可
to call myself a magician anymore
就因为 那件事
'cause of the whole... Thing.
别担心
Don't worry.
把我看做是精神向导
Think of me as a spiritual guide.
我允许我这样自称的
I'm allowed to... Call myself that.
谁都可以 也没什么意义
Anyone can. It's meaningless.
你看他金光闪闪的小发箍 蛤蟆
Look at his shiny little hat, toad.
瑞比特
Ribbit.
那个人是谁
Who's that person?
他是蛤蟆 他很酷
It's toad. He's cool.
瑞比特
Ribbit.
别问
Don't ask.
他是个蟾蜍
He was a toad.
我施了一个咒
I did a spell...
把他变成了类人的东西
turned him into a human-ish... Type thing.
那么 是的 我把它变了
So, uh, yeah. I flipped it.
很棒的呀
That's very good.
好吧 我能为你们做些什么
Anyway, what can I do for you gents?
嗯 不是什么大事 真的
Well, it's... No big deal, really.
我们只是 在附近
We were just... in the neighborhood,
嗯 我只是纳闷
and, um, I was sort of wondering,
你懂得 为什么我长成了酱紫
you know, why I am the way I am,
他说过你可以帮我
and he mentioned you might be able to help me.
赞安诺什么忙都能帮
Xanax can help anything.
好极了
Wonderful.
喝了点儿风
Bit of wind there.
哦
Ooh.
好的 我们开始吧
Right. Let's get you started.
这就是 那种令人作呕的小作坊 不是吗
This is a... Kind of disgusting little workstation, isn't it?
你看那个卫生间 它是个窗户
You see the toilet? It's basically a window.
是 我说的窗户 是指墙上的洞
And by "Window," I mean "Hole"... in the wall.
它管用的
It works.
最起码其中一个管用
One of them.
哦 蛤蟆发现了它 你会喜欢的 不是吗
Oh. Toad spotted it. You'd love that, wouldn't you?
把这个放进去
That goes in.
好的 再这样
Ready. Let's do this.
哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦哦
Oooooooooooh.
现在 念咒语
Now the magic words.
阿布阿卡达布拉
Abracadabra.
阿拉卡砸姆
Alakazam.
哈布拉咋达布拉 福利拉你马哈姆
Habrazamdabra, flanimal ham.
哦哦哦哦哦
Oooooh.
现在试试这个 它有魔力的
Try that now. It's all magic.
-那 我只要 把那个喝下去吗 -是的
- So, I just... Drink that down, eh? - Yeah.
-直接从食道咽下去吗 -是的
- Straight down the gullet? - Yeah.
-哦 很刺激 -是的 里面有肛门
- Ooh. That is pungent. - Yeah. That's the anus.
哦 不管啦
Oh, what the hell.
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
嗯
Mm.
呼
Hmm.
只需一会儿就效果强烈
Takes a little while to kick in with a strong-willed...
-我能感觉到它 -是的
- I'm feeling it. - Yeah.
哦 喔
Oh, wow.
好的 老大 我们需要一个逃跑方案
All right, boss, we need an escape plan.
-你在想什么 -伽尔凡特 我是这么想的
- What are you thinking? - Galavant: Here's what I think.
如果你真的打破这牢笼
If you really break it down...
“我像爱任何人一样爱你”
"I love you as much as someone like me could love anyone"
可以有很多含义
can mean a lot of things.
哦 不是吧 伙计
Oh, come on, man.
哦 放手吧
Oh, just let it go!
她不配的
She's the worst!
-她囚禁了我们 -她偷走了我们的珠宝
- She imprisoned us. - She stole our jewels.
-是的 不喜欢 -你想知道我想什么吗
- Yeah, not a fan. - You want to know what I think?
我想 你在一个地牢里
I think you're in a dungeon
想知道那个关你的女人是否爱你
wondering if the woman that put you there loves you.
真正的问题是 你为什么还爱她
And the real question is, why do you still love her?
我的意思 的确 她很美
I mean, yes, she's beautiful,
完美的皮肤 完美的身体 完美的头发
in a perfect-skin, perfect-body, perfect-hair kind of way,
如果你好这口的话
if you're into that sort of thing.
嗯
Mm.
我了解你的 伽尔凡特
I know you, Galavant.
我懂你的心 你值得更好的人
I know your heart, and you deserve better.
你值得一个能提升你 让你变得像个男人的人
You deserve to be with someone who will lift you up as a man,
一个可以和你并肩战斗 而不是对抗你的人
someone who will fight with you, not against you.
也许某个小巧而机灵
Maybe someone who's small and cute
本性很难被约束的人
and ethnically hard to pin down.
你的意思是
What you're saying is...
你认为她不爱我吗
you don't think she loves me?
我的天啊
Bloody hell.
哦 请不要折磨我 杀了我吧
Oh, please, just stop the torture and kill me already.
我还没有开始呢
I haven't started yet.
他不是一伙的么
He's not part of it?
所有人都闭嘴
Will everybody just shut up?!
-你想知道什么是真正的折磨吗
- Do you want to know what real torture is?
-不 不用了 谢谢
- No, I'm good. Thanks.
想象一生只对某个人忠诚
Imagine being loyal to someone your whole life.
我不准备告诉你是谁
I'm not gonna tell you who,
但假想下 我们都称呼他国王
but hypothetically, we'll call him "The king."
他有点像男妓 但我蛮喜欢他
He's a bit of a ponce, but I like him.
他和那个屁股像篮子贝壳的女人结婚
Then he gets married to this rump-fed basket cockle,
某人 假想下 我们称呼她女王
who, hypothetically, we'll call "The queen."
我们都知道你说的是谁 加雷斯
We all know who you're talking about, Gareth.
但让我神秘一会儿 好吗
But let me be cryptic for a minute, will ya?!
就让我神秘一会儿
Just give me that!
接着说 她不像国王
Now, she's not like "The king."
但她强壮 我的力量陷入泥潭
But she's strong, and I mire strength.
而且 还有 我已经宣誓保护国王
But, then again, I've sworn an oath to protect the king.
所以我不知道该怎么办
So I don't know what to do.
我是说 这才是真正的折磨 不是吗 兄弟们
I mean, that's real torture, isn't it, lads?
欢迎来到理查德的旅行
Welcome to Richard's journey
去发现他为什么是现在的样子
to find out why he is the way he is.
随手可以拿到瓶瓶罐罐的药水
There's bottles of water in easy reach.
请保持水分
Please stay hydrated.
不要接吻
And no kissing.
当然了 等等 什么
Of course. Wait. What?
哦 应该不成问题
Oh... Shouldn't be an issue.
但过去发生过这种情况
But it has happened in the past,
所以我定了一个规则 禁止接吻
so I made a blanket rule... no kissing.
唔 好主意
Mm. Good idea.
好的 大家准备好了吗
Okay. Everyone ready?
瑞比特
Ribbit.
#闭上双眼 打开心灵#
# Close your eyes, open your mind #
#美妙旅程 将要开启#
# Your journey's about to begin #
#心怀善缘 不要怨气#
# Relax your karma and try not to barf #
#周身一切开始天旋地转#
# As the universe starts to spin #
#天灵灵 地灵灵 梦中一切快显灵#
# Hocus-pocus, expealadocious #
#抛开顾虑#
# Set your aura free #
#通通石化 金杯深饮#
# Petrificus totalis, drink deeply from the chalice #
#急急如律令#
# Tell us what you see-e-e-e-e-e #
我看到了一扇门诶
I see a door!
噢 我刚才怎么说来着
Oi! What did I say?
别闹
No...
从这扇门走进去
Go through it.
竟然自动打开了
It's opening on its own!
这就是魔法
That's magic.
这是我父皇驾崩之日
This is the day my father died.
#吾王已逝 吾王万岁#
# The king is dead, long live the king #
#子嗣何在 即将登基#
# Where is his son, who'll inherit everything? #
那是你吗 大人 真是帅到没朋友
Is that you, sire? So handsome.
不是 他是我长兄 金斯利
No. It's my much older brother, Kingsley.
-我什么都看不见   -那才是我
- Young Richard: I can't see anything! - That's me.
#安静点 孩子#
# Shut up, you #
我什么都看不见
I can't see anything!
#安静点#
# Shut up #
噢 天呐
Oh, dear.
吃饱了我就不难过啦
I ate my feelings.
面包多着呢
And a lot of bread.
#您的御剑 陛下#
# The sword, Your Highness #
#帝王之剑#
# Here's the royal sword #
我不需要给来的东西
No one gives me anything.
#欲掌其位 必佩其剑#
# To be the king, you must receive the sword #
我想要的话 我会亲自夺过来
If I want something, I take it.
再说我也不想当什么国王
And I don't want to be any king.
噢 可是 金斯利 天降大任于斯
Oh, but, Kingsley, it's your destiny.
我们依据字面之意为你取名金斯利（国王之地）
We literally named you "Kingsley."
这是上天的旨意
God told us to.
不是说为了赶时髦
It's not like we were being trendy.
我的宿命不是坐在这城堡里  母亲
My destiny lies beyond the castle walls, mother.
我要四处征战讨伐 斩杀敌人
I'm going to conquer and kill
还要在这片土地上播撒出更多私生子
and spread bastard children throughout the land,
就如野花种子布满大地
like wildflower seeds.
总有人能坐上王位主持朝政的
Somebody else can sit on their ass and rule.
#那是何人#
# But who? #
#何人 何人#
- # Who? # - # But who? #
#是谁 那是何人 那是何人#
# Who? # # But who? # # But who? #
迪仔
Dickie?
"Dickie."
好极了
Brilliant.
加雷斯
Gareth.
在
Aye.
你即刻起即为禁卫侍从
You shall be the king's guard.
我才十岁 但  好吧
I'm only 10, but... All right.
我是加雷斯 我将为你鞠躬尽瘁 忠贞不二 陛下
I'm Gareth, and I'll faithfully serve you, My King.
#御剑 陛下#
# The sword, your highness #
#帝王之剑#
# Here's your royal sword #
#欲掌王位  你必#
# To be the king, you mu... #
事实上 我觉得这把剑还是我来拿吧
Actually, I think I will take the sword.
祝你好运 迪仔
Good luck... Dickie.
太丢脸了
How humiliating.
就这么走了
That's it.
当时也太丢脸了
It was humiliating.
一切都追溯于这个时刻
Everything comes back to this moment.
我这一辈子的时间
I have spent my entire life
都在让人觉得我是备胎
behaving as if I'm everyone's second choice...
我父母这么认为 我的子民这么认为 现在我的王后也是如此
my parents', my kingdom's, and now my queen's.
我要夺回我的王位
Let's go take back my kingdom!
那道该死的门在哪
Where's that bloody door?
好吧 我们究竟要怎么回到那里
Well, how the hell are we supposed to get up there?
太神奇了
That was amazing!
多谢你 赞安诺
Thank you, Xanax.
我现在清楚我要做什么了
I now know exactly what I must do.
来吧 厨子 到马棚去
Come on, chef! To the horses!
现在最好不要骑马
I wouldn't ride just yet.
再说了 这是个关于合法的问题
Again, it's a legal thing.
曾经有个家伙 骑着他的马穿过集市
A guy once... he took his horse through a farmers market,
然后当时就有人“啊”的惊叫
and there was... "Raaaaaah!"
马蹄乱踏 乱成一片 四下尖叫 所以
The hooves and the crushing and s-screaming, so...
-呃 -等魔法药水的药效慢慢减退吧
- Ugh... - Let the potion wear off.
就一个小时 怎么样
An hour, say?
噢 好吧
Oh. Okay.
嘿 既然这样的话
Hey, in that case, you guys
你们想看看我小时候的房间么
want to see my room from when I was a kid?
哇
Wow.
那 那就去吧
Let's... let's do this.
太棒了
Great.
听着 伽尔凡特
Listen, Galavant...
我知道之前我的所作所为很过分
I know what I did to you was horrible...
或许比玛达莲娜更过分
probably even worse than what Madalena did to you,
因为至少她还敢当着你的面做出那些事
because at least she had the guts to do it to your face.
我也不想再提起
And I won't say it again,
但不告诉你这些我会更难过
but I'm more sorry than you'll ever know.
我只想让你知道 我真的很抱歉
Just so you know... I'm really sorry.
噢 天哪 你现在心情一定很糟糕 你又在说个不停了
Oh, God. You must feel really bad. You're babbling.
你心情不好的时候就会开启话唠模式
You only babble when you feel really bad.
我心情不好的时候才不会话唠
I do not babble when I feel bad.
我不是说这有多么不好
I'm not saying it's a bad thing.
说实话 我已经学会去接受了
To be honest, I've rather grown to like it.
不过你确实很话唠 公主
But you do babble, princess.
话唠公主
Princess Isa-babble.
"Princess Isa-babble."
好吧 等一下
Okay, hang on a sec.
话唠的意思是说一堆废话
Babbling is when someone talks nonsense,
而我从不说废话
and I do not talk nonsense.
我是说 有时候 偶尔那么几次 我可能是话有些多
I mean... Sometimes, at times, I guess I do babble,
但那只是因为脑子里的事山路十八弯
but it's only because I have a lot going on in my head and...
算了不说了
oh. Never mind.
听着 你没必要觉得难过
Look, you don't have to feel bad.
他们是你的父母
They're your parents.
当你在乎别人时
When you care about somebody...
你愿意为他们奉献一切
You'll do anything for them.
爱就是这么神奇
Love is... Strange.
不过有时又让人厌恶
And sometimes kind of gross.
#废话连篇 真是尴尬#
# It's embarrassingly gassy #
#只留下肮脏的内衣#
# And it leaves its dirty underwear #
#堆满一地#
# In piles around the place #
#爱很鲁莽 又有某种气味#
# Love is rude, it has a sort of smell #
#或许人们对爱未曾留意#
# And it thinks that you don't notice #
#有时脱口而出#
# And it blurts out things #
#令你恨之入骨#
# That make you want to smack its stupid face #
#爱 令人尴尬而又令人困惑#
# And it's awkward and confusing #
#令你恼羞成怒#
# It annoys you half to death #
#然后又呆呆咧嘴而笑#
# Then it grins that dopey grin #
#令你无法呼吸#
# And you can't catch your breath #
#爱很神奇  有时又飘飘乘风起#
# Love is strange and sometimes sort of smug #
#异常专横#
# And it's really, really bossy #
#又会扰乱你的思绪#
# And it messes with your head #
#直到你绝望到无以复加#
# Till you're a hopeless basket case #
#还冥顽不灵#
# And it's stubborn #
#十分无礼#
# It's insulting #
#无比可憎#
# It's obnoxious #
#没有比它更糟的#
# It's the worst #
#你一直将它拒之门外  然而你却一头载入爱的怀抱#
# You keep pushing it away, and you fall in headfirst #
#爱情如此不可思议#
# Love is strange #
#还总是一副醉醺醺模样#
# And often pretty drunk #
#淡妆浓抹总相宜#
# It looks different without makeup #
#与童话故事相去甚远#
# And it's nothing like the fairy tales #
#你梦想着爱成长#
# You grow up dreaming of #
#爱很诡异#
# Love is weird #
#爱很愚蠢#
# Love is dumb #
#爱很神奇#
# Love is strange #
#这就是爱#
# And that's what makes it lo-o-o-o-o-ve #
我真是太糊涂了
I've been so blind.
玛达莲娜从来没有爱过我
Madalena never loved me.
当你心有所属  你会在房顶大喊其名
When you love someone, you shout it from the rooftop,
而非在谜语里闪烁其词
not couch it in a riddle.
或是在歌声里
Or in a song.
那就更煽情了
That's more cinematic.
那么时机怎么样
Well, how's that for timing?
就在我即将死去之时
Our stars are finally aligning
我们的命运之星终将并成一行
on the same day I'm going to die.
不
No.
不  你今天不会有事的
No, you're not gonna die today.
今日你也会安然无恙
And you're not gonna die today.
你也死不了
你或许早已成了行尸走肉
You might already be dead.
那 接下来你有何打算
Well, what are you going to do?
还能有什么打算
What else?
力挽狂澜咯
Save the day.
这门就这么一直开着么
Have these been open the whole time?
就没人想过要检查下么
No one thought to check?
不是吧
Really?
完事了吗 对他们上刑了么
Is it done? Did you torture them?
没有
Nah.
但我下了命令
But I gave you an order.
我特么才不叼你的狗屁命令
I don't give a rat's ass about your orders.
你可以说我是狗 但至少我忠贞不二 亲爱的
I might be a dog, but at least I'm a loyal one, love.
如今 我效忠陛下 我只听从他的旨意
Now, I serve the king, so I only follow his orders.
你这么说我真是太高兴了
That is so nice to hear.
一直以来你都是我最忠诚的友人 加雷斯
You have always been my most loyal friend, Gareth.
我知道你不喜欢拥抱 不过假如你喜欢的话
I know you're not a hugger, but if you were,
我会给你一个结实的熊抱
I would wrap myself around you
像由爱缝制而成的皮夹克一样紧裹着你（嚓 好基情）
like a leather jacket made of love.
嗯
Mm.
赞安诺干的
Xanax?
-绝壁是他 -嗯
- So much Xanax. - Mm.
好 有几件事情要交代下
Okay, couple of things.
首先 厨子 我快要饿晕了
First, chef, I am so munchy.
你能不能给我来点 比如 一盘美味煎蛋卷
Could you make me, like, a cheesy omelette
要加些火腿肉 炸土豆 上面浇培根油
with some ham chunks, potatoes fried in bacon grease?
-我立刻就做 陛下 -好极了
- Right away, sire. - Excellent.
接下来 我们分手吧
Next, I'm breaking up with you.
加雷斯 能不能请你把玛达莲娜护送到地牢里
Gareth, would you please escort Madalena down to the dungeon
把她一辈子拷在那
and lock her up forever?
怎么样
Huh?
走吧
Come on.
等等
Wait!
我们的来宾如此特别
It would be rude to imprison your queen
在这个时候囚禁你的王后可就太残忍了
when we have such a special visitor.
什么访客
What visitor?
你到底在说什么
What are you talking about?
好久不见 老弟
Hello, brother.
金斯利
Kingsley?
他在这做什么
What's he doing here?
你在此有何贵干
What are you doing here?
我来此可是来了结你的
I'm here to take your life.
杀了我
My life?
剥夺你的帝王生活
Your lifestyle.
你的王国
Your kingdom.
如果你阻扰我的话
Of course, if you get in my way,
我也不得不了结你的性命
I'll have to take your life, too...
迪仔
Dickie.
这下好玩了
This is gonna to be fun.